Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 40, folder: (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Parties To Dispute: System Federation No. 114, Railway Employes' Department, AFL-CIO Southern Pacific Company (Pacific Lines), Publication (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Parties To Dispute: Transportation-Communication Employees Union (Formerly The Order Of Railroad Telegraphers) Union Pacific Railroad Company-Eastern District, Publication (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: Parties To Dispute: Railroad Yardmasters Of America The Texas And Pacific Railway Company, Publication (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Box: 41, folder: 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Challenge: Effective Employee Communications in Labor Negotiations, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    By J. E. Wolfe. June 14. Item is in English.
- Box: 41, folder: 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: More Fireman Featherbedding?...a threatened return to the horse and buggy era!, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Questions And Answers AboutRailroads And Employes, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: SafetyNot An Issue, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Railroad LaborLaws And Procedures, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: History OfFeatherbedding Fight, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Box: 41, folder: 3 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Colleges And Universities Reporting Major Curricula In Recreation, Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Recreation Personnel Service of the National Recreation Association, Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Forced Union Membership Steals Your Freedom, Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Here are The Essentials Of A Good Recreation Department, Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Recreation An Essential Part of the City Plan, Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Recreation A New Profession in a Changing World, Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Box: 41, folder: 4 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agreement, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Mediation Agreement, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Mediation Agreement, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Arbitration Board No. 298, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
    July 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Mediation Agreement, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Agreement, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Mediation Agreement, Case No. A-7128, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Mediation Agreement, Cases A-7127 And A-7128, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Chronological Record Of Fact-Finding Decisions On Fireman Manpower Issue, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Mediation Agreement, Cases A-7127 And A-7128, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Box: 41, folder: 5 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A New Medium Of Communication Between Employer and Employee, Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Something Can Be Done Business Climate, Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Service is our businessThe story of National Research, Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Check List Of Employee Rights, Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Check List Of Employee Rights, Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: do you want your rights protected?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Service is our businessThe story of National Research, Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Box: 41, folder: 6 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Educational Aids for schools and colleges, Publication (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Box: 41, folder: 7 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Personnel Service Personnel Group, Publication (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: joining NRMA automatically adds over 100 professional consultants to your staff., Publication (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Put these experts on your staffbut NOT on your payroll, Publication (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Dear Retail Merchant:, Publication (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Box: 41, folder: 8 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: What do YOU want in aa New Labor Bill?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Box: 41, folder: 9 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Consumer Checklist For Purchasing Prepaid Legal Services, Publication (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: A New Bargaining Focus on Legal Services, Publication (Box 41, Folder 9)
    By Sandy DeMent. May. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Clearinghouse, Publication (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Clearinghouse, Publication (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: A New Bargaining Focus on Legal Services, Publication (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Box: 41, folder: 10 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Glimpse Into The National Restaurant Association, Publication (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Box: 41, folder: 11 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: NRA News, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: NRA Washington Report, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: NRA Washington Report, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: NRA Washington Report, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: NRA Celebrates 50th Anniversary, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: NRA News, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: NRA Washington Report, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: NRA Washington Report, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
    May 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: NRA Washington Report, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: NRA News, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: national restaurant association news, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Box: 41, folder: 12 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: List Of Publications, Publication (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Promotion Exchange, Publication (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Would You Invest just a little for Valuable Ideas?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Preliminary Program 45th annual convention, Publication (Box 41, Folder 12)
    January 9-12. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: What The National Retail Dry Goods Association Can Do for Your Store, Publication (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: What The National Retail Dry Goods Association Can Do for Your Store, Publication (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Box: 41, folder: 13 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Board Of Directors, Publication (Box 41, Folder 13)
    November 16-20. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: What Your National does for you and your industry, Publication (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Box: 41, folder: 14 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Rights And Obligations of Retail Lumber Dealers under The Labor Management Relations Act, 1947, Publication (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The Status of Retail Lumber Dealers under the Fair Labor Standards Act of 1938 And The 1949 Amendments An Analysis of Wage-Hour Division Interpretative Bulletin, Part 779 "Retail And Service Establishment And Related Exemptions", Publication (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Box: 41, folder: 15 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Who Speaks For The Consumer?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Retailing Serves America, Publication (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Washington News Letter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: NRMA Flash Bulletin, Publication (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Box: 41, folder: 16 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: May We Serve You?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: NRMA, Publication (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Box: 41, folder: 17 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 13: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 15: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 16: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 17: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 18: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 19: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 20: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 21: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 22: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 23: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 24: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 25: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 26: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 27: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 28: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 29: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 30: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 31: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 32: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 33: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 34: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 35: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 36: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 37: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 38: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 39: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 40: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 41: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 42: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 43: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 44: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
    February/March. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 46: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 47: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 48: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 49: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 50: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 51: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 52: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 53: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 54: The Nation's Press and Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 55: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 56: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 57: Right To Work News, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 58: MEMO, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 59: State Locals Balk UAW On Dues Hike, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 60: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 61: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 62: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 63: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 64: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 65: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 66: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 67: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 68: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 69: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 70: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 71: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 72: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 73: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
    June 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 74: free choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 75: Management and The Right To Work, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
    By Reed Larson. June 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Should Americans Be Compelled To Join Labor Unios, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 77: free choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 78: free choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 79: free choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
    February 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 80: free choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
    August 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 81: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 82: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 83: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 84: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 85: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 86: Free Choice, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Box: 41, folder: 18 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Foundation Action in the Courts, Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: National Right To Work Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: National Right To Work Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Box: 41, folder: 19 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Voluntary Unionism For Free Americans, Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
    By John E. Coogan. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Do Right To Work Laws Hurt Or Help The Economy?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: National Reight To Work Committee, Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: America's Choice: Right To Work Or Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Check-Off, Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: National Right To Work Committee, Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Box: 41, folder: 20 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Program 41st National Safety Congress And Exposition, Publication (Box 41, Folder 20)
    October 19-23. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: National Safety Council catalog of Occupational safety services, Publication (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Proposed Changes In The Constitution And By-Laws Of The National Safety Council, Publication (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: National Safety Council, Publication (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: See Think Do, Publication (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: New Slide Show And Safety Brief On Safe Driving, Publication (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: See Think Do, Publication (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Box: 41, folder: 21 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: the New 354 page Supervisors Safety Manual, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Keeping Posted, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Annual Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Wood Products Section, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Automotive & Machine Shop Section, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Wood Products Section, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Wood Products Section, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Wood Products Section, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Report To The Nation 1964, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: National Safety Council Report to the Nation, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Box: 41, folder: 22 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Careers in Electronic Data Processing, Publication (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Box: 41, folder: 23 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Condition Of Farm Workers In 1956, Publication (Box 41, Folder 23)
    By Fay Bennett. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Condition Of Farm Workers In 1955, Publication (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Box: 41, folder: 24 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: ABC Of Politics, Publication (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Do We Want Wage Incentives?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 24)
    By John A. Patton. May 14. Item is in English.
- Box: 41, folder: 25 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Ethics for Engineers, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Policy Statements Collective Bargaining Professional Provisions Of Labor Legislation Unionization Of Engineering Technicans, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Code of Ethics For Engineers, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Professionalism Or UnionismWhich choice for the Engineer in Government?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Next StepRegistration!, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: National Society of Professional Engineers, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
    By Paul H. Robbins. April. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Constitution and Bylaws, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: Policy Statement Engineering Titles, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Ten Steps to a Professional Engineer-Management Relationship in Industry, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: Professionalism or Unionism-Facing the Issue, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
    By T. Carr Forest, Jr. March. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Engineering A Career Of Opportunity, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 12: Engineering Employment Practices Bibliography, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 13: Recommended Grades, Duties, Responsibilities And Qualifications For Pre-Professional And Professional Positions, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 14: Policy Statement Engineer-Management Communications, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 15: Tabulation of Unions Representing Engineering And Technical Employees, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 16: The Professional Engineer In Industry, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
    By Paul H. Robbines. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: next stepRegistration, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 18: Every Man A Debtor, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 19: Statement of Policy Professional Responsibility vs Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 20: Q&A Registration For Engineers In Industry, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 21: Conference Proceedings Management-Professional Employee Relations, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
    May 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Index To Minutes Of The Meeting Of The Board Of Directors, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
    October 19-21. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Conference Proceedings Professional Development The Responsibility of Industry and th eEngineer, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 24: Policy Statements Professional Responsibility vs. Collective Bargaining Professional Provisions Of Labor Legislation Aid To Engineering Technicians In Opposing Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 25: Statement of Policy Professional Responsibility vs Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 26: Q&A About Registration For Engineers In Industry, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 27: Where Do You Stand As A Professional?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 28: Why Join a Professional Society?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 29: Policy Statement Engineering Titles, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 30: Policy Statement Engineer-Management Communications, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 31: Government Professional Development Policies, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 32: The Importance of Membership, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 33: Consulting Engineering Services, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 34: NSPE And You, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 35: National Society of Professional Engineers, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 36: The Professional Union A Contradiction, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
    By Clarence T. Shoch. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Professional Responsibility vs. Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 38: Policy Statements Collective Bargaining Professional Provisions Of Labor Legislation Unionization Of Engineering Technicians, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 39: "Engineer", Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 40: A Vital Decision For: the engineering technician Trade Unionist or member of the Engineering Team?, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 41: What NSPE Does For The Engineer In Government, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 42: The Open Door, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 43: Whose Job To Teach Professionalism, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
    By Paul H. Robbins. October. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Federal Security Clearances And The Rights Of Employees, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 45: For The Engineer In Industry, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 46: The Engineering Union-Dinosaur in the Space Age, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 47: executive order handbook, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 48: newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Box: 41, folder: 26 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Relationships With Employees, Publication (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Engineer-Management Communications, Publication (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Box: 41, folder: 27 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: Engineering Employment Practices, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: Engineering Employment Practices, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: Engineering Employment Practices, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 9: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 10: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 11: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 12: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 13: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 14: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 15: Engineering Employment Practices, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 16: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 17: Engineering Employment Practices, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 18: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 19: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 20: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 21: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 22: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 23: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 24: Engineering Employment Practices, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 25: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 26: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 27: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 28: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 29: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 30: Engineering Employment Practices, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 31: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 32: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 33: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 34: Dear Sir:, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 35: Engineering Employment Practices, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 36: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 37: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)